There's only curry powder that I've eaten.
카레왕 가루만 있어요 어 내가 먹었던 거는 안에 있었는데 카레왕 가루만 있나요
No, this isn't it. This is what you made, and it's just the mouth of curry king.
아니죠 이거 아니요 일분이 만드신 거고 카레왕의 그냥 그대로 만든 입이요
Monsieur Munchkin.
가가없는 모스밥먹이습니다
So-hui made the most of the cutlassfish today.
오늘 소희가 제일 좋하는 가래비을 일단계로 하셨는
There are a few. The first step is to refer to the period of the Silla.
몇기거든요 일단계는 참고로 신라한 정도의 몇기니다 이거
There's a lot of hook-ups with hookers, so if you go to the pit, you're gonna have to do it.
많을 후레이크랑 하는 꽁짝니다 그니까 아비고 가시면은 꼭세요 꽁짜니까
So-yeong is the best, but if you have avocados curry, you don't have to ask her to eat.
소영이가 제일좋하는 건데 아비고 카레가 있으면 형상 밥을 먹으라고 안 해도
I keep telling you to eat it in the cage, but if you make it look like you're eating it all the time,
형소에는 먹으라고 계속이하지 먹어 그대신 소이가 맨날 먹자 그려가지고 소하면
If you think about what to eat when you're at home with your son, just pretend to be worried about it.
수양이한테 집에 있을 때 뭐먹을까 이러면은 이초 고민하는 척하다가
Let's go eat. Then we can't order.
먹을까 이래 가서 먹자 그러면은 시켜먹으면 안돼 그래서 는 제일
I mean, if you eat it, it'll be too much of a hassle.
게 아비고를 시켜먹는 거요 아 시켜먹으면 스력이 너무 귀찮아 나가서 먹자면
Even if it's burnt, the environment is bad.
타도 기름이 들어가지고 환경이 안 좋은데 시켜먹는 것도
It's hard to clean up because there's a lot of trash.
찮다고 한경지길려가는 게고 쓰레기 많이나와서 치우기 귀찮해서 그래그니까아빠 한번만
That's why I'm not letting you take it out.
그래가지고 전에 이양물고 받게 테고나갈라고 아냐
That's why I put the next one up again, and I'm annoyed because I tried to take it back and bring it to you.
먹어야도 그래서 같는데 차기를 놓고왔네 다시 올라갔다  가지고또 데려가려고 하니까 짜증나서
There's a lot of sauce in here, so if you go and eat it, you can just go.
이게 시켜만쓰리가 진짜 많이 나요 가서 먹으면 먹꾸 그냥  가
If you order from a foreign country, I'll get hurt.
치우잖아  여국기서 시켜먹으면 내가 다치하잖아
In the past, when I was a king, the owner of Ibis in Interiguous City...
옛날에 왕심님 살때 인터식스에 있는 아비고 사장님이
He's kind of nice, but he's got a lot of cavities in each region.
친절는데 아비구가 엄청 많화요 각지역기 하나시타있어요 이게 원래 매운카레로
And, uh, So-yeon's favorite thing is when you go and eat, you can use the menu.
거더라고 그리고 소연님가 아비고 좋아하는 게 가서 먹을 때는  메뉴를 쓸수하셔 자가
All right, let's do this. First, baby, stir-fried egg.
걸 좋아요기본칼의 단계 아기 토핑 계란 날달결 음료
I mean, it's always that way, but curry is expensive. I just want the basic curry.
항상 그렇겠서 근데 카르지 입 비싸 기본 카레가 할래 국물만 있는 거야 그게
How many times do you have to do that? Then, when you're done with the bamboo shoots, it's going to cost 10,000 won.
얼마들라 실천 삼벽은 그면 건대기 듬면 이제 얘는 만원까지 가는 거 비북카레라고
That's one of the basic cars with a bit of bib on it.
거는 기본카에다 비쁘가 들어가 있는 일중에 새트 매뉴 같이 된 거지 근다 그래
This is the only soup in the carapace, right?
카르집은 다 이번이 국물만 있잖아 그죠 나인날에 흥대 살도 있죠 자혀할 때 우리 집
There was that. It was a halibut restaurant, and there was this kiosk.
그거 있었어 무슨 할레집인데 이스크가지게 되 있어가지고 이름이 모였더라
That's right. It's a parakeet. How do you know there's only soup?
맞저 파쿠물리 맞져요 어떻게 알아서 거기도 국물만 있는 게 있었었거든
I feel like I've never heard of her before.
당 딱 느꼈죠  내가 기존히 알고수던 칼래 굉장히 그냥 감편하게 부담없이
But after seeing the curry that's aged for three days, it's not that easy.
말아서 먹는 거 근데 삼일씩 숙성하는 카레를 딱 보고나서 아 카레가 만만한 게 아니구나
I realized that I had to eat a big bowl of rice later.
큰만 먹고 먹어야 되는 요리구나 그걸 제 깨달았지 나중에 곡고 이지방야
When you eat it there, it's just that you put it in one or two toppings, and if you go to the countryside, you'll find a place like this.
거기서 먹을 때는 맘짝물라으 토핑 한두에 집어 넘으은 그냥 막 만우천는냐 곡고 이지방야 가면은
There's one thing that bothers me the most when I don't look at them.
거들도도 안 보면서 이게 땡기는 게 하나 있거든요 아습하라고스 이상하게 아습하라고스
I don't even eat it, but it's humid there, so I'm just waiting for the sign.
먹지도 않는데 거기이 아습하라고스 되게 말수 보지 국기만 기다 있으니까
I think we need to match the viscosity with the raccoons, but it's so expensive that when we eat curry,
야체랑 러스를 맞춰야 될 것 같고 데 그렇게 비싸 그래서 카레를 먹을 때는 비상카를를
You can't just eat it when you're in the mood.
때는 그냥 먹음안 되고 와인
You have to eat it. Take it off, take out the documentary. Just take a quick, high-speed camera.
먹어야 돼요 벗서 다기멘터리  벗서 피 오르는 것 막 빠른 초고속카메를 밖에 하지  피
It's the only thing you can do. And the surface is hardened, and it's hard to stop it.
그러 만있는 것잖아 카래가 막고  표면이 막 굳어가지고 밖에 주은 막되게 빨리 막지나 엄청 그
You hit him without any sign of sinus, and you made him look like a dead man.
제료 악지없이 때려 봐아가지고 다 가아가지고 죽처럼 만들어서 이 애기스가 축된
Imagine it, it's not just us. It's a bunch of nutrients.
상상을라 이건 그냥 우리 아니다 영양분 덩어리 물리다 이 생각을 하면서
I mean, it's not that bad.
돼 그려가져 카려가 훨씬 말죠 아비고 그 매장 가면 항상 그 옆에 붙했거든 어떤 할아버지가
From the curry I made above, it's been passed down to the nuna, so until now.
위에 만들었던 카레에서부터 시작해서 누와구가 아직까지 전해져서 이십 몇까지
I put it in and aged it for 14 hours.
넣어가지고 사십팔시간 동안 숙성을 시킨 후
The dumpling soup made by me tastes good.
만들어진는 달세 국물이 게 맛있다 할리는 언저제 먹으도 시근데
I mean, it's kind of like this all the time, but these days, I've been able to make that retort a lot better, and I think that's why I'm here.
다 먹고 나서 이런 말락인 좀 그렇지만 요즘에 그 레토트도 원낙 잘만들어가지고 카레왕하고
Well, it's been a long time since I've been here, and it was there in the middle of Indiana.
뭐들라 옛날라 무슨 된리카레였나 뭐 그 있었는데 중간에 한번 인틀리카에
It's expensive, but curry is expensive. It's 15 years of aging.
엄청 다영하고 것도 하시는데 비싸 카레왕 비어요 사십팔시간 숙성은 그 카레왕도
I'm going to dry it down a little bit, okay?
정도 숙성할 걸요 레용 한가 카려 그쳤는데 그래 이거야
Sweet and sour dakgalmi is here, but it's sold in direct-fired soybean sauce.
상큼한  다콤 마 이거 마있는데 직곡코 청정어에서  출시
Kara brand. It's a little expensive compared to kara.
카래 브랜드요 어떻게 카레이 비해서 값이 좀 비싼편이다 외운마 조절 가는 우리사를 너을
Karev, I have a theory of karate.
칼래 나는 카레다따라는 컨습을 짓고 있는데 나가수의 자은 이혼단들이 나가수에서 했던
I mean, it's in the report to the KARA, and it says,
패로디하며 카레이대에 평가에 내용으로 나니다 동시간테 경장프로 그램 일박이를
More like curry sold in the UK.
이생기 매인 모들이었다 더봐 영국에서 파는 카레고 비슷하잖아 이거 지금 얼마에
With all due respect, Apple uses its own marinade to make it deeper and deeper.
정성스럽게 우려엔 애플엔 헌이 육수리 사용해서 더욱 깊고 부드로운
No more mops, no more apples, the sweet mop of the oyster, and the kids' mouths.
카래 몇지 않고 사과가 벌굴의 달콤한 마으로 아이들이 입마에도 오케
You can have a softer scallop scent, and you can add a soft taste to your taste.
더 부드운 카래 취주 파우다가 별처으로 들려있서 취향이따라 부드어운 맛을를 더할 수 있음
There's a crack in the crack, and Apple Lance can't pay for the curry.
벌굴이 들어가 애플랜 헌이 카레 가격은는 안 수 있지 열개 야
Look at this. There's a sheet of paper in there.
천음백원 이거 봐 야체도 같이 들어있는 거거든  안에
You know, it's not like you're actually selling kalguksu.
야무지다 야무저 실제 판매되는 카레한 구은만을 양파로 촬영한
It's okay, but it's not like there's a potato in there.
데 카레이 들어가는 단근엔 그래도 찮아 감자아 있는 것보다 감자 단근 이렇기 좀 섞개다가있어
I'm supposed to make curry udon a little bit.
한되게 원래 이제 카레우동은 좀 물게 해야 되거든요 요거를
I felt it while eating at Abigail, but the viscosity is much different.
제가 아비고에서 계속 먹으면서 느낀 건데 점도가 달라 점도가 훨씬 물거  이거는 그냥
I've spent a lot of money on it, but it's too much.
몇만 투와했죠 이러데 너무 구떻해 카레만 판매의 상품 건등이 별두로
No, it's inside a gondola, and I added it as a garnish, right?
아닌데 건대기도 안에 있는데 이고 별두로 추가했다고 이거를 가루 있는 거야 카레왕
There's only curry powder.
있어요 카레왕 가루만 있나요 어 가루만 있네 어 내가 먹었던 거는
There's only powder, and the retrostor's actual report.
있었는데 가루만 있는 것도 있고 레토로트 실제 보고서이거
This isn't it. This is what you made.
이거 아니요 일분이 만드신 거고 카레여왕의 가가없는 모습
I don't want to eat this, but there's dried pollack broth in the soup.
뭐 이런 이거 부고도 안먹고 싶어 풍두북 육수가 들어간 거야 오분에 국은 소곡이
The only stir-fried yoke is the one that makes the onions and the backbone of the onion soft and savory.
볶끈 야체 만을 양파 허부등을 늦고  구들고 고소하게 만든 정통프랑스씩
I want to see the real thing, not this one.
육수잖아 이거 말고 실체가 보고싶은데  그냥 그대로 만든는 님이요
I used a barbeque broth. Why would you do that?
폭두보 육수 사용했고요 자  아 왜 그대로를
I want you to make it as it is. It's like a mart.
만들지 어좀 그대로 만들로으면 좋겠는데  마트 같다 옷두이
It's twice as expensive, but if you buy it in a bad mood, it's just as swollen.
두배 비싸기 하지만 뭔가 다르겠지 뭐라 죽겠찮는 마음에 사보시면 냥 붓기만
But this isn't powder. It's not a powder, it's a dumpling soup.
데 그치 이거 가루 아냐 가루여왕 아냐  폭두부 육수란이걸를
You have to look at this. It's more delicious. You always have homework.
봐야 돼 이걸 봐야지 더 맛있어죠요이걸 항상 숙제 알라고 여 풍트보
I put in the stir-fried pork belly and half of the onion.
뭐라고요 부깊자의 볶 야체와 반을 양파 허부등을 넣고
You have to read this if you're a nutritionist.
정통프랑서실 갈색 욕습니다 요걸 꼭 읽어야 돼  영양성분다면 보고
I bought it with powder.
가루로 사서 건대이
So there's only one thing that keeps getting late on the powder and the indigo knife.
것도다붙이하는 것 같애 그래서 가루에다가 계속 늦는 것만 있구나 이거랑 인대리칼에
This was the original copper mine from the Fair Trade, and the Amitya Indian.
이거는 제일 제당에서 낸 거 원랜 내도였는데 아테 인도가 될리를
I'm getting married to an Indian. It's expensive.
인델리라는 말을 제대해서 고 그래 비싸서 이천는 선가지로
You know, it's expensive, but this name makes it more expensive.
비싼가 하는데 너무하에 그래 이런 거 이 이름이 더 사고시게 만들었어 더
You look professional. I liked Demi-Croissants.
전문화된 것 같잖아 데미커리 알루리 빈달로거리 좋아했는데
I don't know what to do with it.
뭐 있는데 어떻게 만들르고 있는 거야 없어는데 알루커리
You know, kyakari, when you were growing up, you grew up with rice paddies.
하시지 키악리란 곡기 야책콩을 자게 다졌다는 흰두
It blends well with the Indian spices Mahalaya, which is very fragrant.
어로 인도전통 향신료 마살라와 잘 오울러져 향이 진나게 살아있는 인도
There's a margaritas in there, and the energy drinker says Alura is an alkaline potato.
거리이니까 마살라가 들어가 있어요 힘악커에는 알루 거리란 알루 감자라는 뜻으로
You know, in the North, it's almost every day, every morning, when you go to harvests and stuff like that,
북부지방에에서 거의 매일 먹년 일상적인 거림 이런 거에다가 할리라가면
I don't want you to call me Curly, then I'll be your wife.
커리라고 불러할 안해주세요 그러면 순님 거림니다 알았으니까 하리하
It's yours, but I really had a word with you because it's expensive.
님 것은니다 아근데 고 진짜 말있었어요 가격이 비싸서 그렇지
There must have been a cuckoo ring. It's just that there's something like this.
수유칭이 있었을 것이다커리가 할게 이렇게 게 있다고해서 이게 그냥일반
The general soup can be expanded, but it can also expand.
아니라고 일반 국물이 안내를 확대 할게 있지 근데 이걸도 확대
There are so many good medicinal herbs in here.
이 안에는 엄청 몸에 좋은 약큐들 약제들이 차 있다는 거야 몸을 막
What's good about oxygen is that it contains a lot of sodium.
산소들 뭐 있잖아 좋은 거 나트료 미내라 이런 것들이 잔택 들어있다는 거야
It's a common practice to cut more than thirty-five percent of the spices here and there.
이십까지 이상의 제료를 곱게 갈라서 여기다  쳐원학기 때에 일반적이 그냥
No, it's not. There's an effect of the adhesions, and in that case, Kara can just scoop up the soup.
아니다 영향과동어리 실전 악추가 애끼스라는 것죠그렇게 때 카리는 그냥 국물만 퍼먹거도 된다
I didn't even know it was there.
야심자 크래프트카리 한번 보이죠 그래프트카래까지만 국까 나 이거 있는지도 몰랐다
Yeah, well, how did curry go down there?
네 그래 어떻이 카레가 서 공격을 당했잖아 프리미명카래 내볼법도 하거든 그래프트
Gratte jjajangmyeon, but I only eat crayons.
그래프트 짜장 근데 커리라고 안하네 난 커리만 먹는데 육시계 얼마야
It's expensive. It's like a thousand karev's.
비싼에 카레왕 천 배원었는데 싼척했네 알고고 십
That's what it's all about.
되는 것였서 천삼명 그래 이게 맞지 아까 거기가 좀면 비싼되지 그래프 난
It's not her. It's her name.
커리가 아니라서 카르라서 로안된기고 인델리는 살라졌서도 그 유지를 있는
Let's just get a little distance. This is a carburetor.
거리 한번 붙그래  커리만 먹어 이게 전지형카램가보다
If it's curry, it costs 10,000 won. Wow.
좀네 카레면 천 오거인데 와 이렇게 나온다고
There's a street, and you've actually tried green beans.
거리도 있고  그린커리 실제로 먹어봤잖아요
I'm gonna meet her. I'm going to see her, and she's gonna be like, "Hey, you know, it's not like that."
가라는 만나요 만나고 이럴 거 하잖아 야체만나고 그렇치가 않아 아예 막
I ate it in Thailand, but the Indian restaurant is a little expensive.
이질적있는 잖나 어 태국에서 먹었어 근데 그 인도식당은 좀 비싸 가서
It's a little expensive, but if you eat it with halal, it's worth 10,000 won.
좀 비싸요 난에다가 할레하나에다가 한둘이 찍킨 게해서 먹으면은  만 오천는
It's hard to say what it's like to be a human being with a lot of chives.
인당 치히킨이 나운데 많호처님 상거 아니까그까 어떤 느낌이냐면은  사람이케
You know, if you eat six or seven people in a row, it's too much.
잖아 커리를 국 게 탄둘이 여섯개 세명이 먹어도 인당 만우처는 너무가인드율이
It's expensive these days.
비싸요 요즘 일국법 만원인뒤 요즘에 국바 국르이 일반
I don't know what you're doing, but it's gonna cost you a thousand won, right?
뭐얼만지는 모몰르겠지만 특은 천원 추가잖아 그치 원래 그게 국르를하냐
This is an unusual amount of rice soup, so even if it's 10,000 won, there's a lot of expensive food.
이 특이 이천원 추거들라 그래서 국밥도 만원인데도 되게 많어 비싼되 있지 비싼데
The high-end rice soup restaurant is like that. It's like 10,000 won, and it's a rice noodle soup with rice.
고급국밥집은 만 이천 원 막 그렇게 가고 만 오천원 도가고 후리미형 국밥죠
In the past, it was a price range of 9,000 won Korean pork cutlet restaurants, more like China.
그나옛날에 왕심이 살 때 가격고지 오천 원 국밥집이죠 더 중국이었나
All right, well, this is what this place really is, and it's not burdensome.
한녕되죠 이게 여기가 사 여기는 진짜 헌색 자체가 부담없이파는
I didn't know how much it was worth.
데라서 아  팔천 원이에요 팔천 원까지 몰랐어요나쁘지 않죠상찰리
It's not bad to eat it like this, anyway, it's the best place to live.
되어서 이렇게 먹으면 나쁘지 않죠 아무튼 여기가 싼편냐 딴데 비해서 제일산집이라고
It definitely feels like Delhi.
거요 디하시하시하는 확실히  인델리에 느낌이 있네요우둘투드란 느낌으로
It feels like it's connected to the Insilk, Ji-Hui.
게 인들리칼에 이어받든 느낌이다 깨애가 지 희아 이야기 이런 거 이게
I didn't know that long ago, but there's something like this behind the back of the jjajangmyeon when I eat.
있어야 돼 난 옛날에 몰랐는데 후장지 뒤에 이런 게 있어야지 먹을 때 좀 더 직중에서
You can eat it. There's a picture of you.
먹을 수 있죠 픈님 사진다 하나다 있고 일본 숙성카레의 우리지널인기마는 인도 왕실의
It's a dish that you've been cooking for a long time in Agar.
아그라에서 오랜시간 숙성시킨 카레분을 활용에 즐기던 요리로 연극을
It is the aged caratrice of Tiamasai, which is made of the scent of fire in Japan.
일본을 너마가 불라운 색을 진 숙성 카려가 됐습니다 티아시아키하은 로스티드비프의
It's a seasoned curry that adds marmalade to your mince.
라이지한 양파로 마에 기필를 더던한 숙성카레입니다 로스티디비프는
But why do you want to do that?
근데 왜 로스티드비프에 국분 소곡 복꾸 양하잖아 내 그 커리니까
It's different. You talk about Helmut Pankov, and in the memoir of Chelsea's debutante, there's a lot of spinach.
다르죠 헬락판이를 이야기 첼시이 발다한 혼자보에서는 시금치를 곱게 가라놓
If you enjoy it, the city will be full.
즐기면 시지가 울러저 부드었고 순남마이 일품 티아시아 플락판일에는
It's a softer Indian style of stir-fried chicken with arabic tea.
크림 치제풍미를 더의 부드로운 인도시 커리니다 아라시랑 같이 먹어 되고요
This is Salahadin. It can be made by the Sindhu.
활용해서 어울 기업해다 이게 받을셀라드요 만들수됐어요 민달로
I enjoy cooking with spicy peppers, among them Marie Nadeen.
매콤만 고추가 들어간 요리를 즐기입니다그중에서도 마리 네이드한
It's a street that goes well with spaghetti, and it's called Chilcottino Marto.
스파이시한 상신료가 어울러진 거리가 유명합니다 티아시아 빈달로는 하칠리아토마트로
It's a spicy spicy stir-fried chicken with mustard sauce.
맞을 살린 매운 인두식 커리입니다 막근히 후민형 네임이죠
Tampara cream on the tundra in India, the main road of the town.
몇근이 지킨 몇근이는 거리의 본고장 인도 될리에서 탄들이 지킨의 트마트 크림
Tommaso and Gómez.
맞는 것에서 유리에 됐습니다 토마트와 고서 그림 여으러진 말든 인도식
It's like reading this one by one, but when I changed to someone else,
요런 거 한번씩 읽어주는 거요 부 다른 사람로 바꼈때 작만
I changed it. In Thailand, this is Thailand.
바꼈는데 아 태국 이건 태국이라 그래 이건 부바폰 거리라 품이 바껴서
If you put it in that earfucker, it wouldn't have been a credit.
오히로 뒤데일이죠 이거 똑같이 아가 그 이셔프님으로 넣으면 신용이 안 갔지 푹바봉으로
He changed his mind, and then he returned to India.
픈님 바꼈지 그러다가 다시도 인도로 돌아같 하시에 다음에 이
If you give me one more day, I'll be with Cori.
거리 그만에 하루주면 코리기 말을고요